Hello everyone and welcome back to EnglishPod.
大家好，欢迎回到EnglishPod。
My name is Marco.
我是Marco。
And my name is Catherine and today we have an advanced media level lesson so that's the
我是Catherine，今天我们有一个高级媒体课程，这是
very highest of our levels.
我们最高级别的课程。
Right.
没错。
And we're going to be talking about a very popular tradition in North America, a Thanksgiving
我们将讨论北美一个非常流行的传统——感恩节
dinner.
晚餐。
Okay, so Thanksgiving is a very special holiday for Americans and Canadians also celebrate
好的，感恩节对美国人来说是一个非常特别的节日，加拿大人也庆祝
it.
它。
And different dates, right?
而且日期不同，对吧？
Canadians have it on a different date.
加拿大人在不同的日期过。
In fact, I'm not sure what the Canadian date is but Americans celebrate it at the end of
事实上，我不确定加拿大的日期是什么，但美国人在11月底
November.
庆祝。
The day changes every year because it's a Thursday.
日期每年都变，因为它是星期四。
But we usually have the day off from work or school and we all eat together and celebrate
但我们通常不用上班或上学，大家一起吃饭庆祝
the year and celebrate the harvest and celebrate our families and friends.
这一年，庆祝丰收，庆祝我们的家人和朋友。
So this tradition of Thanksgiving, what do you commemorate or what do you celebrate?
那么感恩节这个传统，你们纪念或庆祝什么呢？
Well, we actually celebrate the first harvest that the pilgrims had when they were right
嗯，我们实际上庆祝的是清教徒们刚下船
off the boat in New England.
在新英格兰时的第一次丰收。
So that's the eastern part of America.
那是美国东部地区。
These people had come from England and they were trying to find a new land and a new life
这些人从英国来，试图寻找一片新土地和新生活，
and they ended up in the Massachusetts area and they didn't know how to farm.
最后到了马萨诸塞地区，但他们不知道如何耕种。
They didn't know how to work the land.
他们不知道如何耕作土地。
And so the Native Americans who were living there at the time helped them out, helped
所以当时住在那里的美洲原住民帮助他们，
them grow corn, helped them find out how to use the land in a productive way.
帮他们种玉米，教他们如何有效利用土地。
And so when that first harvest happened, everyone was able to grow, it was actually a year after
所以当第一次丰收来临时，每个人都能种出东西——实际上是在他们到达一年后——
they arrived, everyone was able to grow corn and food and crops and then they all shared
每个人都能种出玉米、食物和庄稼，然后他们一起
a meal together to celebrate this wonderful occasion.
分享一顿饭来庆祝这个美好的时刻。
Wow.
哇。
And it actually helped them survive the winter because most of the pilgrims, most of the
这实际上帮助他们度过了冬天，因为大多数清教徒，大多数
settlers, they died during the first winter.
定居者，在第一个冬天就死了。
And so this was a really great, great thing for them.
所以这对他们来说真是一件非常非常棒的事。
Wow.
哇。
That's really interesting, an interesting aspect of history and why this is celebrated
这真的很有趣，是历史的一个有趣方面，以及为什么这个节日主要
mostly as you say in North America and Canada and that's why many other countries don't
像你说的在北美和加拿大庆祝，这也是为什么很多其他国家
really have it.
没有这个节日。
It's a popular get together and what you usually have is a turkey, right?
这是一个流行的聚会，通常你会吃火鸡，对吧？
Exactly.
没错。
So a turkey is a very big bird and they go gobble, gobble, gobble, gobble.
火鸡是一种很大的鸟，它们会咯咯叫。
And they have that kind of really red long kind of thing on their necks and big tail
它们脖子上有那种长长的红色东西，还有大尾巴
or big tail feathers.
或大尾羽。
And they're delicious.
而且它们很好吃。
But the funny thing is about turkey that there's a chemical in it that makes you very sleepy.
但有趣的是，火鸡里有一种化学物质会让你很困。
Well, not a chemical, there's a protein in it that makes you very sleepy.
嗯，不是化学物质，是一种蛋白质让你很困。
Oh really?
哦，真的吗？
I didn't know that.
我不知道。
So after you eat dinner on Thanksgiving, everyone falls asleep on the sofa.
所以感恩节吃完晚餐后，每个人都在沙发上睡着了。
Well, Thanksgiving meals in the United States are very, very big.
嗯，美国的感恩节餐非常非常丰盛。
They're very elaborate, right?
它们很精致，对吧？
You'll not only have turkey, but you have pumpkin pie and you have mashed potatoes and
你不仅会有火鸡，还有南瓜派、土豆泥、
gravy and just like a table full of food.
肉汁，就像一桌子的食物。
Exactly.
没错。
And it's a way to celebrate, well to give thanks for all the things that you have.
这是一种庆祝方式，嗯，感谢你所拥有的一切。
And so we like to cook a lot of food to celebrate that.
所以我们喜欢做很多食物来庆祝。
And they're all fall foods.
而且它们都是秋季食物。
So squash, pumpkin, potatoes, things like that.
比如南瓜、土豆之类的。
Alright.
好的。
So we have a dialogue here.
我们这里有一段对话。
So it's just that.
就是这样。
It's a guy who is preparing a turkey dinner and also preparing pumpkin pie.
是一个人在准备火鸡晚餐，也在准备南瓜派。
But he's doing it in a very peculiar way.
但他用一种非常奇特的方式在做。
So why don't we listen to the dialogue and then we'll come back and just talk a little
所以我们为什么不先听一下对话，然后回来再聊聊
bit about the different terms that he used.
他用的不同术语。
Hello everyone and welcome back to our show.
大家好，欢迎回到我们的节目。
Today we are going to learn how to cook the perfect Thanksgiving turkey.
今天我们要学习如何烹饪完美的感恩节火鸡。
I will share a secret that I have kept for over 30 years on how to cook the perfect,
我将分享一个我保守了30多年的秘密，关于如何烹饪世界上
most mouthwatering, juiciest turkey in the world.
最完美、最令人垂涎、最多汁的火鸡。
Let's get started.
我们开始吧。
First of all, we must bring out our key ingredient, whiskey.
首先，我们必须拿出我们的关键配料——威士忌。
You see, the grains used to make whiskey along with the alcohol brings out the flavor of
你看，用来制作威士忌的谷物和酒精能带出
the turkey meat.
火鸡肉的风味。
Let's pour one cup of whiskey on the turkey and serve yourself a cup as well.
让我们倒一杯威士忌在火鸡上，也给自己倒一杯。
Cheers!
干杯！
Ah, that's good 12 year whiskey right there.
啊，这真是好12年威士忌。
Okay, back to our turkey.
好了，回到我们的火鸡。
Preheat your oven to 475 degrees Fahrenheit.
将烤箱预热到475华氏度。
Now have another cup of whiskey.
现在再喝一杯威士忌。
Now that the oven is hot, we place our bird on a rack inside a roasting pan.
现在烤箱热了，我们把火鸡放在烤盘里的架子上。
Let's add some whiskey to give it some extra flavor.
再加点威士忌给它增添风味。
And let's have another cup.
我们再喝一杯。
That hit the spot.
真过瘾。
There we go.
好了。
We can leave it in there for the next 45 minutes.
我们可以把它放在里面烤45分钟。
In the meantime, let's have another sip of whiskey and start with our delicious pumpkin
与此同时，我们再喝一口威士忌，开始做我们美味的
pie.
南瓜派。
Lightly whisk together two eggs and the extra yolk in a large bowl.
在一个大碗里轻轻搅拌两个鸡蛋和一个额外的蛋黄。
Once that's ready, we can put sugar, spices such as cloves, grated nutmeg, and cinnamon
准备好后，我们把糖、香料如丁香、磨碎的肉豆蔻和肉桂
with some cream and dark rum into a saucepan.
和一些奶油及黑朗姆酒放入平底锅。
Gently bring up to simmering point, stirring occasionally.
慢慢加热至微沸，偶尔搅拌。
Now you may notice that we are using some dark rum in this pie.
现在你可能注意到我们在派里用了黑朗姆酒。
This is because the richness of the pumpkin is beautifully enhanced by the dark rum.
这是因为黑朗姆酒能很好地提升南瓜的浓郁风味。
So to celebrate this great occasion, pour yourself a glass.
所以为了庆祝这个伟大的时刻，给自己倒一杯。
Cheers!
干杯！
Now that we have finished with the filling, let's bake the pie for 45 to 50 minutes until
现在馅料做好了，我们把派烤45到50分钟，直到
the filling has puffed up around the edges and the center is almost set.
馅料在边缘膨胀起来，中心几乎凝固。
All done!
全部完成！
A cup of rum to celebrate the completion of this great Thanksgiving dinner.
一杯朗姆酒庆祝这顿丰盛的感恩节晚餐完成。
After waiting for an hour and having a couple of drinks, it's time to check on our turkey.
等了一个小时，喝了几杯酒后，是时候看看我们的火鸡了。
Take the turkey out of the oven.
把火鸡从烤箱里拿出来。
Pick the turkey off of the ground.
把火鸡从地上捡起来。
Don't worry, it will add flavor to this recipe.
别担心，这会给这道菜增添风味。
Now also remove the pie from the oven and serve while still hot.
现在也把派从烤箱里拿出来，趁热上桌。
Cheers and Happy Thanksgiving!
干杯，感恩节快乐！
All right we're back so I think this is going to be one great Thanksgiving dinner for him.
好了，我们回来了，所以我想这对他来说将是一顿很棒的感恩节晚餐。
Oh my gosh and talking about this is making me so hungry.
哦，天哪，说到这个让我好饿。
This always happens when we have food lessons.
每次我们有食物课程时都会这样。
What about do you have any family members who actually drink a little bit too much during
你呢，有没有家人在感恩节期间
Thanksgiving?
喝得有点多？
Yes and I won't say who.
有，但我不说是谁。
So as he was preparing the Thanksgiving dinner, he mentioned a couple of things.
所以在他准备感恩节晚餐时，他提到了一些东西。
For example, a mouth-watering turkey.
比如，令人垂涎的火鸡。
Mouth-watering so this is a way to say appetizing.
令人垂涎，这是一种说开胃的方式。
You know when you see something delicious on TV and your mouth starts to water, you're
你知道当你在电视上看到美味的东西时，你的嘴开始流口水，你
salivating.
在分泌唾液。
It's like your brain is telling you that you want to eat it.
就像你的大脑告诉你你想吃它。
And so your mouth starts to water.
所以你的嘴开始流口水。
So we say that something that's very appetizing, something that looks like it will taste very
所以我们说非常开胃、看起来会非常
very good, it's mouth-watering.
好吃的东西是令人垂涎的。
All right so he was preparing a mouth-watering turkey.
好的，所以他准备了一只令人垂涎的火鸡。
So moving on, he mentioned that he had a key ingredient for his turkey and it was whiskey.
继续，他提到他的火鸡有一个关键配料，那就是威士忌。
Not only whiskey but 12-year whiskey.
不只是威士忌，还是12年的威士忌。
Okay so the thing about whiskey is that oftentimes on the label of a bottle they'll advertise
好的，关于威士忌，通常酒瓶上的标签会标明
how old the whiskey is because you pay more for older whiskeys.
威士忌的年份，因为年份越久价格越高。
They just have better taste in many cases.
很多情况下，年份久的威士忌口感更好。
In this case it's a 12-year whiskey.
这里说的是12年的威士忌。
That means that it was stored in a cask for 12 years to let it age and then they sell
意思是它在木桶里存放了12年来陈化，然后他们才出售
it after 12 years and so that's the special ingredient.
12年后出售，这就是它的特殊成分。
That's the special ingredient, 12-year whiskey.
这就是特殊成分，12年的威士忌。
And well he not only put it on the turkey but also he had a couple of drinks himself
他不仅把威士忌浇在火鸡上，自己还喝了几杯
and in one of those he mentioned that hit the spot.
其中一杯他提到“正合心意”。
That hit the spot.
正合心意。
What spot?
什么心意？
The spot.
就是那个心意。
Okay so this is a really common phrase in English that we use to say that something
好的，这是英语中一个很常见的短语，用来表示某件事
is very satisfying.
非常令人满足。
So that hit the spot.
所以就是“正合心意”。
And not only for drinks right?
而且不只用于饮品，对吧？
No you could use it for food or anything really.
不，也可以用于食物或任何东西。
So in this case I could say, oh so hungry that sandwich really hit the spot.
比如，我可以说，哦，太饿了，那个三明治真合我心意。
I really needed to eat right now and that sandwich was perfect.
我当时真的很需要吃点东西，那个三明治太完美了。
That was perfect.
太完美了。
Alright.
好的。
So that hit the spot.
所以就是“正合心意”。
Now when he referred to the turkey, in one occasion he said we place our bird on a rack.
当他提到火鸡时，有一次他说我们把鸟放在烤架上。
Alright so what's a bird and what's the rack?
好的，那么什么是“鸟”，什么是“烤架”？
Okay so this is really interesting.
好的，这很有意思。
We talk about the turkey often times when we're making commercials or talking about
我们在做广告或谈论食谱时，经常把火鸡称为
recipes as the bird.
“鸟”。
So you want to take out the bird, you want to open the packaging.
所以你要把鸟拿出来，打开包装。
So the bird is the turkey.
所以“鸟”就是火鸡。
A turkey is a kind of bird.
火鸡是一种鸟。
You can say this about chicken as well because it's another kind of bird.
你也可以这样称呼鸡肉，因为它是另一种鸟。
But this is kind of a colloquial term in cooking for whatever bird you're cooking.
但这是烹饪中一种口语化的说法，指你正在烹饪的任何鸟类。
Right.
对。
Okay.
好的。
And when you're placing it on a rack, what's a rack?
当你把它放在烤架上时，什么是烤架？
Okay so in our ovens, an oven is a kitchen appliance that you have that heats up food.
好的，在我们的烤箱里，烤箱是一种加热食物的厨房电器。
But it's not like a microwave, it's much stronger.
但它不像微波炉，它功率更强。
And so inside there are metal bars.
里面有一些金属条。
We don't have, they're like shelves but they're open.
我们没有，它们像架子，但它们是镂空的。
And so these metal bars are called a rack.
这些金属条就叫烤架。
So you put the turkey in the oven on the rack.
所以你把火鸡放在烤箱里的烤架上。
Right, you can't put it on the base of the oven because then it would burn up.
对，你不能把它放在烤箱底部，否则会烧焦。
Exactly.
没错。
And you don't have a shelf because that would be a problem.
而且你也没有实心架子，那会有问题。
Alright.
好的。
And well, moving on the instructions when he was preparing the pumpkin pie, he told
好了，继续看说明，当他准备南瓜派时，他告诉我们
us to lightly whisk together two eggs.
轻轻搅拌两个鸡蛋。
So we have a verb here, to whisk.
这里有一个动词，“搅拌”。
To whisk.
“搅拌”。
So that's not only a verb but a noun as well, right?
所以它不仅是动词，也是名词，对吧？
Alright.
好的。
It's an instrument.
它是一种工具。
Exactly.
没错。
And this is a verb we often use with eggs.
这个动词我们经常用在鸡蛋上。
So to whisk eggs.
所以是“搅拌鸡蛋”。
You can also whisk like sauce for a salad, so like a salad dressing.
你也可以搅拌沙拉酱之类的酱汁。
But it's a way that we stir something.
但它是一种搅拌东西的方式。
And so oftentimes we have an instrument called a whisk that's not like a fork.
我们经常有一种叫打蛋器的工具，它不像叉子。
It actually looks kind of funny.
它看起来有点滑稽。
It's got bars on it.
上面有金属条。
Like wire that kind of make a circle.
像金属丝一样，围成一个圈。
Exactly.
没错。
And they are very thin wires.
它们是非常细的金属丝。
And you usually stir very, very, very quickly.
你通常搅拌得非常非常快。
Especially if you have eggs, this will break up the egg and it becomes kind of like foamy.
特别是鸡蛋，这样会把鸡蛋打散，变得有点泡沫状。
Foamy, yeah.
泡沫状，是的。
To make like an omelet for example.
比如用来做煎蛋卷。
Exactly.
没错。
So to whisk is a kind of, it's a way to stir.
所以“搅拌”是一种搅拌方式。
Okay.
好的。
And then he mentioned some ingredients such as sugar, spices, and grated nutmeg.
然后他提到了一些配料，比如糖、香料和磨碎的肉豆蔻。
So what is this verb, grated nutmeg?
那么“磨碎的肉豆蔻”这个动词或形容词是什么意思？
Or an adjective, grated.
或者形容词“磨碎的”。
Exactly.
没错。
So this adjective, grated, means that, well it's a kind of way to cut up something.
所以这个形容词“磨碎的”意思是，这是一种切碎东西的方式。
And so you often hear the term grated cheese.
你经常听到“磨碎的奶酪”这个说法。
That means not a big chunk of cheese, but we push it against a board to get little pieces
意思不是一大块奶酪，而是我们把它在板上摩擦，得到小块
of it to fall off.
掉下来。
And that's called grated cheese.
那就叫磨碎的奶酪。
And so in this case we have grated nutmeg.
这里我们有磨碎的肉豆蔻。
That means that it's been kind of, the nutmeg comes in, in very small pieces.
意思是肉豆蔻被弄成非常小的碎末。
Yeah, pieces.
是的，碎末。
And we're breaking it down.
我们把它弄碎。
All right.
好的。
Very good.
很好。
And he also mentioned something about bringing the sauce to a simmering point.
他还提到了把酱汁煮到“微沸点”。
What is that simmering point?
什么是“微沸点”？
Okay, simmering point is a time when you're cooking where the liquid goes from being calm
好的，微沸点是指烹饪时，液体从平静状态
to being very agitated and moving.
变得非常活跃和流动的状态。
But it's not boiling, right?
但不是沸腾，对吧？
No, boiling means you have big bubbles.
不，沸腾是指有大泡泡。
Right.
对。
Like boiling water.
比如烧开水。
But simmering is where it's kind of little bubbles, there's a little bit of action on
但微沸是指有小泡泡，液体表面有一些活动，
the surface of the liquid, but it's not boiling.
但不是沸腾。
It's in the middle between flat and calm and agitated and boiling.
它介于平静和沸腾之间。
Okay, so that's the simmering point.
好的，那就是微沸点。
Very good.
很好。
And that's pretty much all of the interesting phrases in the dialogue.
对话中所有有趣的短语差不多就这些了。
There are a lot more, but we don't really have time to cover that huge amount of rich
还有很多，但我们真的没时间涵盖那么丰富的
vocabulary.
词汇量。
Why don't we listen to this dialogue one last time?
我们最后再听一遍这段对话好吗？
Hello everyone and welcome back to our show.
大家好，欢迎回到我们的节目。
Today we are going to learn how to cook the perfect Thanksgiving turkey.
今天我们要学习如何烹饪完美的感恩节火鸡。
I will share a secret that I have kept for over 30 years on how to cook the perfect,
我将分享一个我保守了30多年的秘密，教你如何烹饪出完美、
most mouthwatering, juiciest turkey in the world.
最令人垂涎、最多汁的火鸡。
Let's get started.
我们开始吧。
First of all, we must bring out our key ingredient, whiskey.
首先，我们必须拿出我们的关键配料，威士忌。
You see, the grains used to make whiskey along with the alcohol brings out the flavor of
你看，用来制作威士忌的谷物和酒精能带出
the turkey meat.
火鸡肉的风味。
Let's pour one cup of whiskey on the turkey and serve yourself a cup as well.
让我们在火鸡上倒一杯威士忌，再给自己倒一杯。
Cheers!
干杯！
Ah, that's good 12-year whiskey right there.
啊，这12年的威士忌真不错。
Okay, back to our turkey.
好了，回到我们的火鸡。
Preheat your oven to 475 degrees Fahrenheit.
将烤箱预热到475华氏度。
Now have another cup of whiskey.
现在再喝一杯威士忌。
Now that the oven is hot, we place our bird on a rack inside a roasting pan.
现在烤箱热了，我们把鸟放在烤盘里的烤架上。
Let's add some whiskey to give it some extra flavor.
再加点威士忌，给它增添一些风味。
And let's have another cup.
我们再喝一杯。
That hit the spot.
真过瘾。
There we go.
这就对了。
We can leave it in there for the next 45 minutes.
我们可以把它放在那里，接下来45分钟。
In the meantime, let's have another sip of whiskey and start with our delicious pumpkin
与此同时，我们再喝一口威士忌，开始享用我们美味的南瓜
pie.
派。
Lightly whisk together two eggs and the extra yolk in a large bowl.
在一个大碗里轻轻搅拌两个鸡蛋和一个额外的蛋黄。
Once that's ready, we can put sugar, spices such as cloves, grated nutmeg, and cinnamon
准备好后，我们把糖、香料如丁香、磨碎的肉豆蔻和肉桂
with some cream and dark rum into a saucepan.
和一些奶油以及黑朗姆酒一起放入平底锅。
Gently bring up to simmering point, stirring occasionally.
慢慢加热至微沸，偶尔搅拌一下。
Now you may notice that we are using some dark rum in this pie.
你可能会注意到，我们在派里用了些黑朗姆酒。
This is because the richness of the pumpkin is beautifully enhanced by the dark rum.
这是因为黑朗姆酒能很好地提升南瓜的浓郁风味。
So to celebrate this great occasion, pour yourself a glass.
所以为了庆祝这个美好时刻，给自己倒一杯吧。
Cheers!
干杯！
Now that we have finished with the filling, let's bake the pie for 45 to 50 minutes until
现在馅料做好了，我们把派烤45到50分钟，直到
the filling has puffed up around the edges and the center is almost set.
馅料在边缘膨胀起来，中心几乎凝固。
All done!
全部完成！
A cup of rum to celebrate the completion of this great Thanksgiving dinner.
一杯朗姆酒来庆祝这顿丰盛的感恩节晚餐完成。
After waiting for an hour and having a couple of drinks, it's time to check on our turkey.
等了一个小时，喝了几杯后，是时候看看我们的火鸡了。
Take the turkey out of the oven.
把火鸡从烤箱里拿出来。
Pick the turkey off of the ground.
把火鸡从地上捡起来。
Don't worry, it will add flavor to this recipe.
别担心，这会给这道菜增添风味。
Now also remove the pie from the oven and serve while still hot.
现在也把派从烤箱里拿出来，趁热上桌。
Cheers and Happy Thanksgiving!
干杯，感恩节快乐！
Alright, we're back.
好了，我们回来了。
So Thanksgiving dinner, really popular.
所以感恩节晚餐，真的很受欢迎。
Catherine, have you ever cooked or are you into the whole Thanksgiving feast?
凯瑟琳，你做过感恩节大餐吗？或者你喜欢整个感恩节盛宴吗？
I'm very into it.
我非常喜欢。
It's my favorite holiday in America, mostly because everyone gets to celebrate it.
这是我在美国最喜欢的节日，主要是因为每个人都能庆祝它。
It's not religious, so you don't have to worry about other people not celebrating it or not
它不是宗教性的，所以你不用担心别人不庆祝或者不
knowing what to do.
知道该怎么做。
And it's also a celebration about family and food.
而且这也是一个关于家庭和食物的庆祝。
And so it's just a wonderful experience to have Thanksgiving because you're with everybody.
所以过感恩节是一种美妙的体验，因为你和大家在一起。
And we always say in America that if someone doesn't have a place to go on Thanksgiving,
在美国我们常说，如果有人感恩节没地方去，
you should invite them to your house.
你应该邀请他们来你家。
And so it's a very inviting and warm holiday.
所以这是一个非常热情和温暖的节日。
And I love cooking and I love being in the kitchen and I love having people in the house
我喜欢烹饪，喜欢待在厨房里，也喜欢家里有人
cooking and so yeah, I've definitely been a part of the cooking side of things.
一起做饭，所以我确实参与过烹饪方面的事情。
Now in many movies, they kind of mock this holiday because it's a time where everyone
在很多电影里，他们有点调侃这个节日，因为这是一个大家
gets together, as you say, no matter religion, creed or race.
聚在一起的时候，就像你说的，不论宗教、信仰或种族。
And that also causes for a lot of family members to get together and argue and have discussions
这也导致很多家庭成员聚在一起争吵，讨论
about politics or talk about family problems and stuff like that.
政治或谈论家庭问题之类的事情。
So what do you think of that?
你怎么看？
Well, I think it's an exaggeration, but it happens.
嗯，我觉得有点夸张，但确实会发生。
People get very stressed out during the holidays.
人们在假期里压力很大。
They call it the holidays because this is beginning where you have Thanksgiving and
他们称之为假期，因为这是从感恩节开始，
then later Christmas.
然后是圣诞节。
But I personally don't have experience with that really on Thanksgiving because it's such
但我个人在感恩节上并没有太多这种经历，因为对我们来说
a happy holiday for us.
这是一个非常快乐的节日。
So and in my family, arguments about politics and history and all that is very encouraged.
所以在我家，关于政治和历史的争论是非常鼓励的。
And so it's just a part of the holiday where we have, we have, you know, one person at
所以这只是节日的一部分，我们有，你知道，一个人
the table who says this and the other person says this and you're all drinking and it's
在桌上说这个，另一个人说那个，大家都在喝酒，这
just, it's fun.
很有趣。
I look forward to it.
我很期待。
All right.
好的。
Very good.
非常好。
So if you guys have any other questions or doubts about this holiday, because as we say,
所以如果你们对这个节日有任何其他问题或疑问，因为正如我们所说，
it's very common in North America and Canada, you can come to our website, EnglishPod.com.
它在北美和加拿大很常见，你可以来我们的网站 EnglishPod.com。
And if you have any other questions or suggestions, you can leave those there as well.
如果你有其他问题或建议，也可以留在那里。
We look forward to hearing what you have to say and happy Thanksgiving.
我们期待听到你的想法，感恩节快乐。
Happy Thanksgiving.
感恩节快乐。
Bye everyone.
大家再见。
Happy Thanksgiving.
感恩节快乐。